

WALTER RADDUSO

Frontend Developer

▲ ABOUT ME

When I was younger I loved computers, many years ago I met the language C and created my first application. Then I met PHP and that's when I discovered my real passion, being a web developer. Since then, I kept myself continuously learning and improving the way of writing better code, everyday.

Nowadays I'm dedicated to Frontend development. This is what I love to do most

- **E** CONTACT ME
- Santa Fe, Argentina
- w.radduso@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/walterradduso
- github.com/walterradduso
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- NodeJs
- React
- React Native
- Flutter / Dart
- MySQL
- MongoDB



WORK EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL LEAD FRONTEND

My main role in the company is be the responsible of the frontend development of different initiatives. In this area we are using React and NodeJS. Recently my role became more dynamic executing lots of tasks in different environments.

SSR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Inside of the company I have a very dynamic role, executing lots of tasks in different environments. I was the team leader of a web application created with CakePHP in the Backend and HTML, CSS, JQuery, AngularJS and most recently, VueJs in the FrontEnd. Also, I helped the product manager with tasks like designing new features or validating requirements. I've worked for several months as a FrontEnd developer creating applications using AngularJS, React and NodeJs. I've developed some mobile application using React Native.

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelancer 🛅 Feb 2016 - Jun 2016

I was continued my freelance working. In this case I created the site of the city with a module of news (like a online newspaper) and a internal system to manage the users complain.

WEB/MOBILE DEVELOPER

1st Outsourcing Choice Sep 2014 - Feb 2016

I've been working in an application for swimmers only for iOS (Objective-C). Also in charge of a website in WordPress, we created a plugin which got products from a web application (RESTful API). The plugin created products in woocomerce to sell in the website.

WEB DEVELOPER

Tecnosan 🛗 Oct 2013 - Sep 2014

I've worked on several projects with different business rules and all kind of web applications. My job was to create and maintenance web applications (PHP, HTML, CSS, JS and MySQL).

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelancer May 2011 - Oct 2013

I've been working on several kind of projects (PHP, HTML, CSS and JS), custom and complex WordPress sites, RESTful APIs, and also building entire applications including User Interfaces. One of my own projects was a local e-commerce where users were able to upload products and sell them. The site was used in San Justo, Santa Fe and surrounding area.



EDUCATION

IT SUPERIOR TECHNICIAN

📠 Instituto Superior Nº20

2012 - 2014

SECONDARY SCHOOL

🚓 Escuela de Comercio Dr. Roberto Gonzalez Nº 45 🛮 📋 2008 - 2003



LANGUAGES

SPANISH ENGLISH

NATIVE INTERMEDIATE (B2)